[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann"]}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What are your feelings about what's been happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I think personally what Ann's probably going through is she is determined to show up for work every day, do the great job that she always has been.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ann"]}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Why hasn't it worked?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, I don't think you can lay the blame squarely on Ann's shoulders, although that certainly seems to be what's happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "I mean would it have been fairer to say, as he has said, look, it may be my fault?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, if it's his fault, he's not losing his job so I don't think anybody would agree with him when he says that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Is she the answer, do you think, to whatever problems the \"Today\" show may have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, whatever problems, that's the trouble.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Do you believe that the video proves that he had injuries consistent with a life or death battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, that's truly going to be a decision to be made by the judge or by the jury when they look at this case because the whole issue is whether or not he had reasonable fear of great bodily injuries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "Do you accept that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, I understand his position.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What has been happening to him behind the scenes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "I would have to be -- it would be pure conjecture on my part.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "ORGAN: Do you feel instinctively, when you heard that it was a murder charge, did you feel that the real debate, or to be over a manslaughter charge, that whatever it was, it wasn't murder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, when I -- I think I shared with you when I was the non-lawyer in this case before I was involved in it and heard about the facts leading up to it, and then heard about the charge of second degree, and having had a lot of second degree murder cases, I was curious to see where evidence of second degree would come from.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Do you expect George Zimmerman to be granted bond?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I believe under the law and the case law that he is entitled to a bond.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I'm well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "And how cathartic, if it has been, was writing the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "One of the reasons I chose to write the book was to help me with my personal recovery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Would you think that's a fair assessment, that she just in the end was undone by those demons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "You know, she was troubled with -- with those demons for a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Quite ironic, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, you left a little bit out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "What's the bit I left out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, I can't say on air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Has he ever contacted you, written to you, called you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A.", "Grammys"]}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "But when you heard what happened to Whitney Houston, what went through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "We were -- we were in L.A. for the Grammys.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Tell me this, from what you saw happen to your girl and from what happening to Whitney, Michael Jackson, to a certain degree, and so on, the pressures of being a hugely successful musical star in the modern era, do they bring a very particular stress, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "WP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "It's difficult to say, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"], "LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Why did you feel this was the time to do the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "You know, really, the book came about from years of meeting people along my journey and really hearing from other people their stories of loss and difficulty, and finding that, you know, maybe my story could be helpful to others, so that was really what prompted me to write the book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "What kind of guy was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "He was, you know, one of those people who just really stood out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Why did he feel so strongly, do you think, that he had to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I think after 9/11, like a lot of people, Pat really sort of took a step back and reprioritized what was important to him in his life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "What were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "It's a difficult thing for families, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Did you try and persuade him not to, to start with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "No, I didn't try to persuade him not to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What advice do you give so many other war widows, girlfriends, wives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I think that's the difficult part, is there is no one answer for everyone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "It just made me question everything that we had been told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "You must have felt angry, didn't you, that possibly you'd been deliberately lied to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Certainly there was a mix of emotions, and anger being one of them, confusion, and just, you know, betrayal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "How high do you think it went, the deceit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "You know, I'm not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "When you read that, what went through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Well, when I originally read it, it was something that was very difficult because at that time I didn't want to live.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "CC", ":", "CC", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Do you think he would have instinctively second-guessed how you would feel in that scenario?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "You know, I don't know if that's why he wrote it or if it was just something that he felt like he wanted to leave something comforting and -- and to be able to say, you know, this is what I wish for you if I don't return.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "You say in the book that while Rumsfeld was testifying, you say every fiber in my body was crying B.S. Why did you feel that so strongly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "It was just a really difficult experience to be there and to sit in the back of the room and listen to all of this play out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rumsfeld"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Eight years later, do you feel any closer to knowing exactly what happened or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "You know, it's been actually quite a while since I've seen a lot of that and really sort of relived it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "How hard was it to make that move?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "It was a long journey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]